Guide to the New York Building Congress Photographs PHOTOS.109
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
New York Building Congress Photographs
Bulk, 1950-1998
1936-2008
PHOTOS.109
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
13.0 linear feet (13 boxes)
The New York Building Congress (NYBC) is an association that brings together employers, labor unions, government agencies, engineers, architects, financiers, suppliers, and others engaged in the construction industry in New York City. Founded in 1921, it now has ca. 400 affiliated organizations, with a combined membership of over 250,000 skilled workers and professionals. The Congress engages in educational and lobbying activity, hosts public programs, and disseminates information on issues of concern to the industry. The collection consists of black and white and color photographs (some with negatives) and slides documenting personnel, activities and special events of the Congress, with portraits of noted political figures and other awardees and guests at Congress events. Also included are a small number of images of construction sites and office interiors.
New York Building Congress.
Scope and Content Note
The collection is comprised of the photographs, contact sheets, and negatives of the New York Building Congress. These photographs document administrative meetings of the NYBC and awards dinners, luncheons, and other social events hosted by the Congress, as well as some industry events. Included are portraits of key individuals in the New York City building industry and political establishment. Events such as industry recognition dinners, golf outings, and the Christmas show "Fun and Frolic" are particularly well represented in the collection. “Fun and Frolic” was a comedy revue featuring political satire and musical performances held annually at the Waldorf-Astoria Hotel. Though the shows were written and directed by professionals, all roles (both male and female) were played by volunteer, male members of the NYBC. First held in 1938, the “Fun and Frolic” show was discontinued during the late 1980s.
The majority of photographic prints in the collection are black and white 8 x 10 prints; also included are color prints in a variety of sizes, including 4" x 6" and 3" x 4". Photographs and matching negatives are placed in the same folder, and the presence of negatives is noted in the finding aid. There are a limited number of contact sheets, also indicated in the finding aid. Additionally, this collection includes approximately 500 stereo slides dating from 1952 and 1953.
Series I: Meetings, 1947-1999, consists of photographs of administrative meetings, including those of the Board of Directors and Council of Presidents, as well as a variety of committees.
Series II: Events, 1944-2008, contains photographs of annual industry and social events, such as the Leadership Awards Luncheon, Fun and Frolic, the Industry Recognition Dinner, and golf outings. Also included are special receptions and forums with prominent visiting speakers.
Series III: Portraits, 1936-1988, includes portraits of key individuals in the building industry and political establishment in New York City. Many of these were acquired for use in NYBC publications, especially for publicity on featured speakers at Congress events.
Series IV: Site Photographs, 1948-1974, contains a small number of photographs of construction sites and office environments.
Series V: Other Formats and Oversize, 1943-1988, contains stereo slides produced by the NYBC in 1952 and 1953. The approximately 500 stereo slides document meetings, the annual "Fun and Frolic" (1952 and 1953), and various social outings. Also included in this series are a small number of oversize items and the rolled photographs. Note that approximately 15 tightly rolled photographs, indicated as restricted in the finding aid, are not immediately available for reference use. Please consult Tamiment staff regarding access to these materials.
Historical/Biographical Note
The New York Building Congress (NYBC) is an association that brings together employers, labor unions and federations, government agencies, engineers, architects, financiers, suppliers, and others engaged in the construction industry in New York City. Founded in 1921, it now has ca. 400 affiliated organizations, with a combined membership of over 250,000 skilled workers and professionals. The Congress engages in educational and lobbying activity, hosts public programs, and disseminates information on issues of concern to the industry.
Shortly after the First World War, elements of the American building industry attempted to organize a national building congress. Although the planned national organization was never very active, the impulse was continued by city-wide groups. In New York City, the 47-member NYBC was organized in early 1921. Originally, membership was limited to organizations (labor unions, businesses, government agencies, etc.), but it was soon opened to individuals, and its early presidents were noted architects. On this broad basis, NYBC united labor and employers, as well as members of multiple professions involved in the building industry. One of the NYBC's key roles in its early years was to mediate between labor and management.
The NYBC issued a code of ethics for the building industry during its inaugural year, and remained actively involved in setting industry standards. The organization concerned itself with specific building practices; it commissioned research, published reports, lobbied, and spoke out on legislation and regulations pertaining to the industry. The NYBC took a leading role in the revision of the New York City Building Code in the 1960s and also lobbied on more general issues, such as the New York City Charter revision of the late 1980s.
The NYBC has been led in recent decades by Louis Coletti (1986-1994) and then by Richard T. Anderson (1994-present). During this time, the Congress has frequently addressed legislative, regulatory issue, urban developement, and political issues crucial to the industry. A recent Congress intiative was the establishment of the New York Building Foundation (NYBF), which undertakes industry research and philanthropic activities.
Related Material at the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
New York Building Congress Records (WAG 167)
Building Trades Employers Association Records (WAG 196)
Building Trades Oral History Project (OH 45)
The Tamiment Library holds a number of periodicals published by NYBC, including the Building Congress News, Metrobuild, and Edifice
Provenance
The New York Building Congress collection was donated to the Tamiment Library in 1999, through an agreement with Richard T. Anderson, President of the Congress. Additional material was donated in 2009 and 2011.
Access Restrictions
A limited number of restricted materials (approximately 15 rolled photographs) are noted in the container list. Please consult Tamiment staff for access to these materials.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into 5 series:
I: Meetings, 1947-1999
II: Events, 1944-2008
III: Portraits, 1936-1988
IV: Site Photographs, 1948-1974
V: Other Formats and Oversize, 1943-1988
Folders are arranged alphabetically within each series.
Anderson, Richard T. (Richard Theodore), 1940-; Building Trades Employers' Association.; Coletti, Louis J.; New York Building Congress.; Building laws |z New York (State) |z New York.; Building trades |x Employees |z New York (State) |z New York.; Construction industry |z New York (State) |z New York.; New York (N.Y.) |x Buildings, structures, etc.
- Series I: Meetings, 1947-1999
  - Annual Meeting, May 21, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Annual Meeting (Hotel Astoria), May 5, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Annual Meeting (Grand Hyatt Hotel): Richard Green: Prints and Contact Sheets, Jun 20, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Annual Meeting (Includes Marilyn Gelber), 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Annual Meeting: Breakfast Forum: Photos and Negatives, Jan 23, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Annual Meeting, Jan 1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors; Membership and Building Industry Practices Committees, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors (Includes John Dyson), Mar 24, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors, Council of Presidents and Foundation Reception, May 1998 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors (Includes Tony Coles), Mar 24, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors: Prints and Negatives, Sep 19, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Board of Governors: Cocktail Party, Apr 27, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Board of Governors: Meeting: Presentation to Life Members, Mar 28, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Board of Governors: Meeting (Includes Marc Shaw and Stephan R.), Apr 1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Board of Governors and Council of Presidents Meeting: Negatives, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Board of Governors, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Capital Needs Assessment Meeting, Dec 11, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Committee: Economic Development and Energy: Joint Meeting with Con Edison, Feb 5, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Committee: Economic Development; Milos Riverso Forum; Public Buildings Committee: Prints and Negatives, Sep 1998 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Committee: Transportation: Prints and Negatives, Aug 1997 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Committee: Energy, Dec 1997 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Committee: Transportation, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Committee: Education, Dec 18, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Committee: Membership, Feb 13, 1998; Apr 2, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Committee: Public Buildings (Includes Patricia Lancaster), Jan 28, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Committee: Public Buildings, Sep 11, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Committee: Construction Controls, Dec 5, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Council of Presidents: Luncheon, Jun 22, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Council of Presidents: Arthur Levitt, Jr. (101 Club): Prints and Contact Sheets, May 20, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Council of Presidents: Stephen Berger (101 Club), Jun 6, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Council of Presidents (101 Club, Includes Andrew Stern), Sep 23, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Council of Presidents (101 Club, Includes Peter Vallone), Oct 21, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Council of Presidents (101 Club, Includes Sandy Fruchter), Dec 1987 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Council of Presidents (Includes Claire Shulman): Photos and Contact Sheets, Oct 19, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Council of Presidents (Grand Hyatt Hotel, Includes Ass. Marc Alan Siegel): Prints and Contact Sheets, Mar 15, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Council of Presidents: Luncheon: Contact Sheets, Jan 19, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Council of Presidents (Includes C. Wisbal): Prints and Negatives, [1994] (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Council of Presidents: Breakfast Forum with Ruth Messinger: Prints and Negatives, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Council of Presidents: Breakfast Forum, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Council of Presidents: Breakfast Forum: Prints and Negatives, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Council of Presidents: Breakfast Forum with Robert Kiley, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Council of Presidents (Includes Luis Tormenta), Apr 17, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Council of Presidents (Includes Herman Berman): Prints and Negatives, Oct 16, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Council of Presidents (Includes Clay Lifflander), 1996 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Council of Presidents (Includes Fran Reiter), 1996 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Council of Presidents (Includes Frank Lombardi), Feb 19, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Council of Presidents (Includes Harry Spencer), Apr 15, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Council of Presidents, Oct 15, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - [Council of Presidents]: Breakfast Forum (Includes Robert Catell), Nov 13, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Council of Presidents (Includes Cathy Nolan): Prints and Negatives, Nov 13, 1997-Nov 19, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Council of Presidents (Includes Colonel Gary Thomas), Dec 17, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Council of Presidents: Reception, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Council of Presidents: Breakfast Forum (Includes Mark Green and Frederick Ferrer): Prints and Negatives, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Council of Presidents (Includes Brad Race): Prints and Negatives, Mar 20, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Council of Presidents (Includes Joseph Lynch), Apr 15, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Council of Presidents (Includes Kathy Coylde): Prints and Negatives, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Council of Presidents: Breakfast Forum (Includes Carl McCall), May 1998 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Council of Presidents (Includes Deborah Wright), Feb 18, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Council of Presidents (Includes Robert King), Feb 25, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Council of Presidents: Prints and Negatives, Sep 20, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Council of Presidents: Prints and Negatives, Oct 18, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Council of Presidents, undated (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Formal Acceptance of Wage Stabilization Agreement (Office of the Building Trades Employers' Association), Mar 24, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Public Agency Council [on Transportation]: Prints and Negatives, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Public Agency Council: Capital Needs, undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Public Agency Council, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Staff, Council of Presidents and Economic Development Committee (Includes Robert Boyle), 1997 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Unidentified Meeting (Hotel Baltimore), Oct 16, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Unidentified Meeting, Sep 29, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Unidentified Meeting, Jul 2, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Unidentified Meeting, Sep 1976 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Unidentified Meetings, undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Unidentified NY Delegation to Washginton D.C., Feb 10, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Unidentified Presentation, undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
- Series II: Events, 1944-2008
  - Anniversary Dinner (40th, Hotel Astor): Includes Richard A. Wolff, S.F. Voorhees, John Lowry, James Foley, John F. Hennesey, C. George Dandrow, Alan Horowitz, and Bradford N. Clark, Oct 5, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Anniversary (50th), Mar 28, 1971-Mar 31, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Anniversary (50th): Conference, Mar 29, 1971- Mar 31, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Anniversary (60th), Mar 19, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Anniversary (65th): Luncheon (Includes Alfonse D'Amato): Prints and Contact Sheets, May 19, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Anniversary (76th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (1), 1997 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Anniversary (76th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (2), 1997 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Anniversary (76th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (3), 1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Anniversary (76th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (4), 1997 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Anniversary (77th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (1), 1998 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Anniversary (77th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (2), 1998 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Anniversary (77th): Luncheon Committee Kick-Off Reception: Prints and Negatives, [1998] (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Anniversary (78th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (1), May 12, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Anniversary (78th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (2), May 12, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Anniversary (78th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (3), May 12, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Anniversary (78th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (4), May 12, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Anniversary (78th): Leadership Awards Luncheon (5), May 12, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Anniversary (79th): Leadership Awards Luncheon, May 4, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Breakfast Forum (Includes Larry Reuter), Apr 19, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Breakfast Forum (Includes Sheldon Silver), Feb 27, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Breakfast Forum (Alan Hevesi): Prints and Negatives, Jun 1997 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Breakfast Forum (Includes John L. Bruno): Prints and Negatives, Dec 18, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Breakfast Forum (Includes Joel Miele), 1997 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Breakfast Forum (Includes Larry Reuter), 1997 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Breakfast Forum (Includes Joseph Boardman), Feb 19, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Breakfast Forum (Includes Luis Tormenta), Mar 19, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Breakfast Forum (EDC): Prints and Negatives, Feb 23, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Breakfast Forum (Includes Rudy Crew), Mar 19, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Breakfast Forum (Includes Iris Weinshall): Prints and Negatives, Mar 29, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - [Breakfast?] Forum, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Brooklyn Sports Foundation Auction, May 2000 - Jun 2000 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Building Code: Press Conference, Feb 6, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Building Code (1963): Signing (Includes Harold Birm, Charles E. Schaffner and Peter Reidy) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Building Code: Press Conference, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Building Code: Signing, Nov 6, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Business / Labor Breakfast (Sheraton Center, Includes A.L. Delli Bovi), Jan 12, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - City Council: Breakfast: Prints and Negatives, Apr 28, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - City Council: Reception, Apr 1998 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Clark, Bradford: Swearing in as Department of Public Works Commissioner, Oct 13, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Coletti, Louis J.: Testifying before the U.S. House Subcommittee on Health and the Environment, Aug 3, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - C.I.B.D. [Construction Industry Development Board] Summit, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Co-op Holiday Party, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Dinner: Max Foley Jubilee, May 10, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Dinner (Unidentified): Negatives, Jun 1959 (?) (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - [Dinner]: Curtain Call, Dec 1959 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Dinner: Kick-Off Reception, Sep 1998 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - [Dinner: Event with Speakers] (1), undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - [Dinner: Event with Speakers] (2), undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Floyd, William: Farewell Party, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 18, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 18, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 19, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 18, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 21, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 20, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 19, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Fun and Frolic: Rehearsal, Dec 17, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 18, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 18, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 22, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 21, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 20, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 18, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 17, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Fun and Frolic, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 15, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 15, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Fun and Frolic (3), Dec 15, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Fun and Frolic, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Fun and Frolic, [1961?] (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 18, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 18, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Fun and Frolic (3), Dec 18, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 17, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 17, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 15, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 14, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 21, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 21, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 21, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 13, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 13, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 11, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 11, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 18, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 18, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 17, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Fun and Frolic: Prints and Contact Sheets, Dec 16, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Fun and Frolic, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 13, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Fun and Frolic (2): Prints and Contact Sheets, Dec 13, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 16, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 17, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 17, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 15, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 14, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 13, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 12, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 17, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 17, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Fun and Frolic, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 15, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Fun and Frolic (2), Dec 15, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Fun and Frolic (3): Prints and Contact Sheets, Dec 15, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Fun and Frolic (1), Dec 14, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Fun and Frolic (2): Prints and Contact Sheets, Dec 14, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 18, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 17, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Fun and Frolic: Prints and Contact Sheets (1), Dec 17, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Fun and Frolic: Prints and Contact Sheets (2), Dec 17, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Fun and Frolic, Dec 16, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Fun and Frolic (1), undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Fun and Frolic (2), undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Fun and Frolic: Negatives and Contact Sheets, undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - General Events (Identified), 1947-1972, undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Ginsburg, Pam: Birthday Event, Mar 31, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Guggenheim Museum Event, Aug 2000 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Hennessy, John: Party, Aug 20, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Hevesi, Alan: Event: Prints and Negatives, Oct 1998 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Holiday Party, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Holiday Show Entertainment: The Capital Steps (Grand Hyatt Hotel), Dec 20, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Howard J. Rubenstein Assoc., "Rebuilding New York": Contact Sheets, Oct 13, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Industry Recognition Dinner (Grand Hyatt Hotel), Oct 29, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Industry Recognition Dinner Kick-Off: Prints and Negatives, Sep 1997 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Industry Recognition Dinner (1), Oct 30, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Industry Recognition Dinner (2), Oct 30, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Industry Recognition Dinner (3), Oct 30, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Industry Recognition Dinner (4), Oct 30, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Industry Recognition Dinner (5), Oct 30, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Industry Recognition Dinner (6), Oct 30, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Industry Recognition Dinner (7), Oct 30, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Industry Recognition Dinner (8), Oct 30, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Industry Recognition Dinner (1), 1998 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Industry Recognition Dinner (2), 1998 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Industry Recognition Dinner (3), 1998 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Industry Recognition Dinner (4), 1998 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Industry Recognition Dinner (5), 1998 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Industry Recognition Dinner (6), 1998 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Industry Recognition Dinner (7), 1998 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Industry Recognition Dinner (8), 1998 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Industry Recognition Dinner: Kick-Off (Beacon Restaurant): Prints and Negatives, Sep 9, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Industry Recognition Dinner: Kick-Off Reception: Prints and Negatives, Sep 2000 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - John F. Kennedy International Airport Redevelopment: Slide, Dec 1997 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Luncheon, May 21, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Luncheon: NYBC and American Institute of Architects, Jun 26, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Luncheon: Annual, May 5, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Luncheon: Gillroy Testimonial, Nov 10, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Luncheon: New Members, Nov 17, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 8)